Guide to the Lansing V. Hammond Collection of Hugh Thomson
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Artwork, 1879-1923; Series III; 0.6; (2 boxes)
  - ARTWORK BY HUGH THOMSON
    - Illustrations for Books
      - Our Village by Mary Russell Mitford
        - "Making the Cowslip Ball," pen and ink, 1893 Apr
        - "May went to bed," pen and ink, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 239)
        - "The Old House at Aberleigh," pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 240)
        - "Peaceful Evenings," pen and ink, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 241)
        - " 'Prentice to the footman," pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 242)
        - "A Retired Publican," pen and ink, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 243)
        - "That poor boy," pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 244)
        - Two men hunting with dog, pen and ink, 1893
        - "The Visit," pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 245)
        - "Walks in the Country," pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 246)
        - Woman and dog, pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 247)
      - Peg Woffington by Charles Reade
        - "Heading to Chapter III," man, dog and hare, pen and ink and watercolor (Box 6, Folder 248)
        - Initial "Y" for chapter 3, pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 249)
        - Spine decoration and design, pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 250)
        - Tailpiece to chapter 2, woman with cherubs, pen and ink and watercolor (Box 6, Folder 251)
      - The Piper of Hamelin by Robert William Buchanan
        - "By a golden brook," pen and ink
        - Piper with children, pen and ink and watercolor
        - Piper with children dancing, pen and ink and pencil
      - Scenes of Clerical Life by George Eliot
        - "Milly's Grave," pen and ink, 1905
        - "Pushed her slowly before him," pen and ink, 1906
        - "When the lash fell," pen and ink
      - The School for Scandal by Richard Brinsley Sheridan
        - "Act 3, Scene 1: A Room in Sir Peter Teazle's House," pen and ink
        - "Act 4, Scene 1: A Picture Room in Charles Surface's House," pen and ink
        - "Act 5, Scene 1: The Library in Joseph Surface's House," pen and ink
        - "Charles bows ceremoniously to the pictures (Act 4, scene 1)," pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 252)
        - "Sly rogue! Sly rogue! (Act 4, scene 3)" pen and ink
        - "What parchment have we here? (Act 4, scene 1)" pen and ink
      - The Story of Rosina, and Other Verses by Austin Dobson
        - "At the Convent Gate," pen and ink
        - "An Idyll," pen and ink, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 253)
        - "Preface," pen and ink and pencil, 1895
          Inscribed to Mrs. Spielmann, 1899
      - Tales from Maria Edgeworth by Maria Edgeworth
        - "Carolling in honor of the May," pen and ink, 1902
        - "The pet lamb," pen and ink, 1902
      - Tales of the Canterbury Pilgrims by F. J. Harvey Darton
        - "The combat," pen and ink
        - Decorative initial "T," pen and ink
        - "The departure from Southwark," pen and ink
        - "Fell to singing and dancing," pen and ink, pencil and watercolor, 1904
        - Illustration for the list of illustrations, pen and ink
        - "Learning year by year to sing," pen and ink
        - "See friends, he has a waist as large and finely shaped as mine," pen and ink and watercolor, 1904
        - "The Squire," pen and ink and watercolor, 1904
      - Tom Brown's School Days by Thomas Hughes
        - "Each new boy was ... made to sing a solo," pen and ink, 1916
        - "There's two on 'em out and out runners they be," pen and ink, 1916
        - "The little rogue ... would ... stop short and shoot them onto the turf," pen and ink, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 254)
        - "They carry him off to load him with fairings," pen and ink and pencil, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 255)
      - Vanity Fair by William Makepeace Thackeray
        - "I have thanked Sir Pitt Crawley..." pen and ink [reproduction?]
      - Other Illustrations for Books
        - Cover illustration for A Christmas Carol by Charles Dickens, pen and ink, [1912?] (Box 6, Folder 256)
        - Cover illustration[?] for Nicholas Nickleby by Charles Dickens, watercolor, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 257)
        - "An enormously burly thick-set man..." pen and ink. For The King of Hearts by W. O. Tristram, 1888
        - "Holding his son Aaron between his knees," pen and ink. For Silas Marner by George Eliot, 1907
        - "I cannot imagine how they will spend half of it," pen and ink. For Sense and Sensibility by Jane Austen
        - "The little picture girl," pen and ink. For The Rainbow Book by M. H. (Mabel Henrietta) Spielmann (Box 6, Folder 258)
        - Man with two dogs, pen and ink and watercolor. For Wuthering Heights by Emily Brontë, 1899
        - "The Noble Knight and the Virtuous Lady Joyful Spectators of the Giant's Death," pen and ink and watercolor. For Jack the Giant Killer by Hugh Thomson, 1898
        - "Some vulgar dashing widow," pen and ink. For Emma by Jane Austen, 1896
        - Tailpiece for act 4. scene 5 of The Merry Wives of Windsor by William Shakespeare, pen and ink (Box 6, Folder 259)
        - "A Toast!" pen and ink. For The Ballad of Beau Brocade by Austin Dobson, 1892 Aug
        - Woman looking out window, pen and ink. Printed in A Book of Drawings by Alfred Bryan et al, 1891 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Illustrations for Magazines
      - "John Bull's Trip..."
        [Full title: "John Bull's Trip to the Continent," printed in The Graphic, 1897]
        - "Getting Aboard," pen and ink and watercolor, [1897]
        - "John Bull seeing his luggage aboard," pen and ink and watercolor, [1897]
        - "Seeing them off," pen and ink and watercolor, [1897]
        - "Studying Baedeker," pen and ink and pencil, [1897]
      - "Some Board School Children..."
        [Full title: "Some Board School Children" by James Runciman, printed in The English Illustrated Magazine, May 1890]
        - "A Class," pen and ink, [1890]
        - "Culprits," pen and ink, [1890] Jan
        - "Dinner Time," pen and ink, 1890 Jan
      - Other Artwork for Magazines
        - "A Brisk Mover," pen and ink and watercolor. For Stephen Lucius Gwynn's "An Irish Horse Fair," printed in The Graphic, 3 November 1901, 1898
        - Man in chair, and two men at a table, in 17th century dress, pen and ink drawings for Between Ourselves, a Boy's Club magazine
        - Men and women at a dinner table, pen and ink. Printed in Pall Mall Magazine, December 1909
        - "Young Herchard mounted his Dobbin Gray," pen and ink. Printed in The Graphic, December 1895 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Other Artwork by Hugh Thomson
      - "Berwick on Tweed from the old bridge," pen and ink and pencil (Box 7, Folder 262)
      - "The bill next morning," man at desk, pen and ink and watercolor
      - Bookplates of Dale Thomas, Rose Thomas and John Thomson, 1901-09, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 263)
      - "Caclamonos, Leondopolous, and Finance
      - 2 calendars for the Scottish Widows' Fund, 1905, 1906
      - "Carrying fish up from the boats, Holy Island," pencil (Box 7, Folder 264)
      - "Chair! Chaiaw!" man with stick, watercolor, 1883[?] (Box 7, Folder 265)
      - Country dance, for John Milton's "L'Allegro," reproduced for a paper pad cover design, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 266)
      - Gloucester, pencil, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 267)
      - "A holiday in Switzerland," pen and ink, published in The Graphic, [1903] (Box 7, Folder 268)
      - Horseback riders, pen and ink, 1879 Jul (Box 7, Folder 269)
      - House and its grounds, pencil and watercolor
      - "The Inquisitive Ass," watercolor, 1882
      - Invitations illustrated by HT for exhibitions of his artwork, 1899-1923 (Box 7, Folder 270)
      - Man and two children in a garden, pen and ink and watercolor (Box 7, Folder 271)
      - Man with wings, pen and ink and watercolor (Box 7, Folder 272)
      - "Monte Carlo," pen and ink and crayon (Box 7, Folder 273)
      - Photographs of 2 drawings, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 274)
      - Poor family singing in the street, pen and ink and watercolor
      - Postcard with a drawing of Carmichael Thomas's house, with holograph description by MHS, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 275)
      - "Reigate Heath," pencil and watercolor
      - Scrapbook of clippings of illustrations by HT, 1884-1904
        Includes: Illustrations from Art Journal, Black and White, The English Illustrated Magazine, The Graphic, Pears Annual
      - Seaford, pencil and watercolor, 1902 Sep 1
      - Silhouette portrait of Samuel Johnson, pen and ink (Box 7, Folder 276)
      - Sir Harry Lauder, charcoal, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 277)
      - Town Court, Dublin, pencil, n.d.
      - "Young Illigits," pen and ink, pencil and watercolor drawing of an old man with four young ghosts (Box 7, Folder 278)
        Includes: Letter from Percy H. Muir of E. Mathews (Firm) to Lansing V. Hammond, 1950
      - Sketchbook of pen and ink and pencil drawings, including sketches of Sir Harry Lauder (Box 7, Folder 279)
      - Sketchbook of pencil drawings, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 280)
      - Sketchbook of pencil drawings, including drawings of period costumes and furniture (Box 7, Folder 281)
      - Sketchbook of pencil and crayon drawings (Box 7, Folder 282)
      - Sketchbook of pencil and watercolor drawings (Box 7, Folder 283)
        Several drawings are preparatory sketches for illustrations appearing in Scribner's Magazine, April and August 1872
      - Sketchbook of pencil, crayon and watercolor drawings (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - ARTWORK BY OTHERS
    - C. E. (Charles Edmund) Brock
      - "Handing a cup of tea to her admirer," pen and ink drawing of two men and two women at a table
    - H. M. (Henry Matthew) Brock
      - "Why dost thou smile so and kiss thy hand so oft?" pen and ink, pencil and watercolor drawing for Twelfth Night, act III, scene IV
      - Woman with muff, pen and ink[?] and watercolor, on a card with a Christmas greeting (Box 7, Folder 285)
        Includes: Bill from Bertram Rota Ltd. to Lansing V. Hammond, 1955
    - Unidentified
      - "Supper, Sir," watercolor, 1883 (Box 7, Folder 286)
        Originally attributed to HT, but note on back says "The artist's son was positive this was not his father's work"
- Other Materials, 1887-1957; Series IV; 0.4; (1 box)
  - CLIPPINGS
    - About HT, 1896-1957 (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - Reviews of exhibitions, 1887-1931 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Other clippings, 1893-1921, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - EXHIBITIONS OF WORKS BY HUGH THOMSON
    - Catalogs of exhibitions, 1899-1923 (Box 8, Folder 290-292)
    - Invitation to MHS to an exhibition at the First Edition Club (London, England), 1922 Dec (Box 8, Folder 293)
      Includes: Newspaper clipping announcing the exhibition
    - Poster for an exhibition at the Continental Gallery, 1899
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Advertisements for books illustrated by HT, 1908, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Black & White. A Weekly Illustrated Record and Review (London), no. 2, vol. I, 1891 Feb 14
    - The Bookman (London), no. 260, vol. XLIV, 1913 May
      Includes: Letter from The Bookman to MHS, 1921
    - Daily Graphic (London), "Supplement to the Christmas number of The Graphic "
    - Letter to Austin Dobson with a list of people donating money towards a gift, 1910 Jan 18
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, N.Y.). "The Children's Bulletin," Vol. III, no. 4, 1919 Dec (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - The Sphere (London), vol. LXXXVII, no. 1140a, 1921 Nov 28
  - SALES CATALOGS
    - A. & C. Black. "New Books", 1931 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - American Art Association. "Fine Books and Manuscripts of the Greatest Rarity and Interest Including the Further Property of a Prominent Pennsylvania Collector", 1924 Dec (Box 8, Folder 297)
      Includes: "The Village Choir (after Hugh Thomson," pen and ink and watercolor drawing signed "M," 1925
    - Christie, Manson & Woods. "Art Prices Current", 1914 Feb 2 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Sotheby, Wilkinson & Hodge. "Catalogue of Valuable Printed Books...", 1923 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Clipping from an unidentified sales catalog, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - OTHER PAPERS
    - Book jackets for The History of Henry Esmond, Sense and Sensibility, and The Blinded Soldiers and Sailors Gift Book (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Empty envelope addressed to MHS, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Photograph of commemorative diploma from the British Arts and Crafts Exhibition, with holograph notes, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Photograph of Hugh Thomson by E. O. (Emil Otto) Hoppé, 1913 Apr 18 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Photograph of an illustrated "testimonial" letter to James Bresland, with holograph description (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Titmarsh Club (London). Menus for the Twenty-Second Dinner and the Forty- Ninth Dinner, 1920, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Other papers, 1893-1925, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 307)
- Oversize, 3.75; (3 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
  - Letter from HT to M. H. Spielmann (in series I), 1902, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - Hugh Thomson. Galley proofs, corrected (in series II), [1931] (Box 9, Folder 309-313)
  - Hugh Thomson. End paper illustration samples (in series II), [1931] (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Cover originally containing proofs and typescript (in series II) (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Hugh Thomson. Lists of papers to which copies of the book were sent (in series II), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - As You Like It. Man, woman and bird, pencil and watercolor (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Evelina. "Much incommoded by three gentlemen," pen and ink (in series III), 1903 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Evelina. "They frequently looked back," pen and ink and watercolor (in series III), 1903 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Evelina. Woman and mirror, decoration for the list of illustrations, pen and ink (in series III), [1903] (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Highways and Byways... "The Cornish followed the lad up the hill," pen and ink (in series III), 1897 (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - ...Henry Esmond "By the Great Crackling Fire," pen and ink and crayon[?] (in series III), 1904 (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - ...Henry Esmond "Do I look very wicked, cousin?" pen and ink (in series III), 1905 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - ...Henry Esmond "He kissed the fair hand," pen and ink and pencil (in series III), 1904 (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal "Certain Ladies who bow sweetly to me," pen and ink and pencil (in series III), 1900 (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal Headpiece to chapter 6, pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal "I Dressed up," pen and ink and pencil (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal "Little town boys into my strawberry bed," pen and ink and pencil (in series III), 1900 (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal. "Looking down at the gate that I made yesterday," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal. "The New Neighbors have come," pen and ink and pencil (in series III), 1900 (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal. Sketches of decorative initials, pen and ink and pencil (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 331)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal. "Welcomed her gayly," pen and ink and pencil (in series III), 1900 (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - A Kentucky Cardinal. "When she fed her hens," pen and ink and pencil (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - Our Village. "Little Rogues!" pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - Our Village. "Making the Cowslip Ball," pen and ink (in series III), 1893 Apr (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Our Village. Two men hunting with dog, pen and ink (in series III), 1893 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - The Piper of Hamelin. "By a golden brook," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - The Piper of Hamelin. Piper with children, pen and ink and watercolor (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - The Piper of Hamelin. Piper with children dancing, pen and ink and pencil (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - Scenes of Clerical Life ."Milly's Grave," pen and ink (in series III), 1905 (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - Scenes of Clerical Life. "Pushed her slowly before him," pen and ink (in series III), 1906 (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - Scenes of Clerical Life. "When the lash fell," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - The School for Scandal. "Act 3, Scene 1: A Room in Sir Peter Teazle's House," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - The School for Scandal. "Act 4, Scene 1: A Picture Room in Charles Surface's House," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - The School for Scandal. "Act 5, Scene 1: The Library in Joseph Surface's House," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - The School for Scandal. "Sly rogue! Sly rogue! (Act 4, scene 3)" pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - The School for Scandal. "What parchment have we here? (Act 4, scene 1)" pen and ink (in series III) (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - The Story of Rosina.... "At the Convent Gate," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - The Story of Rosina... "Preface," pen and ink and pencil (in series III), 1895 (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Tales from Maria Edgeworth. "Carolling in honor of the May," pen and ink (in series III), 1902 (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - Tales from Maria Edgeworth. "The pet lamb," pen and ink (in Series III), 1902 (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. "The combat," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. Decorative initial "T," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. "The departure from Southwark," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. "Fell to singing and dancing," pen and ink, pencil and watercolor (in series III), 1904 (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. Illustration for the list of illustrations, pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 356)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. "Learning year by year to sing," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 357)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. "See friends, he has a waist as large and finely shaped as mine," pen and ink and watercolor (in series III), 1904 (Box 10, Folder 358)
  - ...Canterbury Pilgrims. "The Squire," pen and ink and watercolor (in series III), 1904 (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Tom Brown's.... "Each new boy was ... made to sing a solo," pen and ink (in series III), 1916 (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Tom Brown's.... "There's two on 'em out and out runners they be," pen and ink (in series III), 1916 (Box 10, Folder 361)
  - "An enormously burly thick-set man..." pen and ink. For W. O. Tristram's The King of Hearts (in series III), 1888 (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - "Holding his son Aaron between his knees," pen and ink. For Silas Marner by George Eliot (in series III), 1907 (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - "I cannot imagine how they will spend half of it," pen and ink. For Jane Austen's Sense and Sensibility (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - Vanity Fair. "I have thanked Sir Pitt Crawley..." pen and ink [reproduction?] (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Man with two dogs, pen and ink and watercolor. For Wuthering Heights by Emily Brontë (in series III), 1899 (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - "The Noble Knight and the Virtuous Lady..." pen and ink and watercolor. For Jack the Giant Killer by Hugh Thomson (in series III), 1898 (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - "Some vulgar dashing widow," pen and ink. For Emma by Jane Austen (in series III), 1896 (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - "A Toast!" pen and ink. For The Ballad of Beau Brocade by Austin Dobson (in series III), 1892 Aug (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - John Bull's Trip... "Getting Aboard," pen and ink and watercolor (in Series III), [1897] (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - John Bull's Trip... "John Bull seeing his luggage aboard," pen and ink and watercolor, [1897] (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - John Bull's Trip... "Seeing them off," pen and ink and watercolor (in series III), [1897] (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - John Bull's Trip... "Studying Baedeker," pen and ink and pencil (in series III), [1897] (Box 10, Folder 373)
  - "Some Board School Children." "A Class," pen and ink (in series III), [1890] (Box 10, Folder 374)
  - "Some Board School Children." "Culprits," pen and ink (in series III), [1890] Jan (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - "Some Board School Children." "Dinner Time," pen and ink (in series III), 1890 Jan (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - "A Brisk Mover," pen and ink and watercolor. For Stephen Lucius Gwynn's "An Irish Horse Fair" (in series III), 1898 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Man in chair, and two men at a table, in 17th century dress, pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Men and women at a dinner table, pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - "The bill next morning," man at desk, pen and ink and watercolor (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - "Caclamonos, Leondopolous, and Finance (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - 2 calendars for the Scottish Widows' Fund (in series III), 1905, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - House and its grounds, pencil and watercolor (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - "The Inquisitive Ass," watercolor (in series III), 1882 (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - Poor family singing in the street, pen and ink and watercolor (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - "Reigate Heath," pencil and watercolor (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Seaford, pencil and watercolor (in series III), 1902 Sep 1 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Town Court, Dublin, pencil (in series III), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - C. E. (Charles Edmund) Brock. "Handing a cup of tea to her admirer," pen and ink (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - H. M. (Henry Matthew) Brock. "Why dost thou smile so..." pen and ink, pencil and watercolor (in series III) (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - Clippings about HT (in series IV), 1896-1957 (Box 10, Folder 391)
  - Black & White (in series IV), 1891 Feb 14 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - The Bookman (in series IV), 1913 May (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Daily Graphic (in series IV), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 394)
  - Letter to Austin Dobson (in series IV), 1910 Jan 18 (Box 10, Folder 395)
  - The Sphere (in series IV), 1921 Nov 28 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Scrapbook of clippings of illustrations by HT (in series III), 1884-1904 (Box 11, Folder 397)
  - Hugh Thomson. Chapter 2, fragment, galley proofs, corrected (in series II), [1931] (Box bsd, folder 398)
  - Poster for an exhibition at the Continental Gallery (in series IV), 1899 (Box bsd, folder 399)
- Restricted Fragile, 0.2; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 33 (Box 12, Folder 400)
  - Box 3, folder 139-140 (Box 12, Folder 401)
  - Box 3, folder 159 (Box 12, Folder 402)
  - Box 3, folder 161 (Box 12, Folder 403)
  - Box 4, folder 186 (Box 12, Folder 404)
  - Box 5, folder 204 (Box 12, Folder 405)
  - Box 5, folder 205 (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Box 5, folder 206 (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Box 8, folder 287 (Box 12, Folder 408)
  - Box 8, folder 288 (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Box 8, folder 289 (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Box 8, folder 302 (Box 12, Folder 411)